<resources>
    <string name="actions">Actions</string>
    <string name="active">Active</string>
    <string name="address">Address</string>
    <string name="adjust_10_degrees">10</string>
    <string name="adjust_25_degrees">25</string>
    <string name="agent">Agent</string>
    <string name="alert">Alert</string>
    <string name="all">All</string>
    <string name="ally_status_ambassador_for_pirate">
        Pirate boss on board. Send shuttle to rescue.
    </string>
    <string name="ally_status_ambassador_for_tsn">
        Ambassador on board. Send shuttle to rescue.
    </string>
    <string name="ally_status_blind">Flying blind. Guide to a station.</string>
    <string name="ally_status_commandeered_in_nebula">
        Commandeered. Approach in nebula to liberate crew.
    </string>
    <string name="ally_status_commandeered_not_in_nebula">
        Commandeered. Do not approach now, or it will self-destruct. Wait until it enters a nebula,
        then approach.
    </string>
    <string name="ally_status_contraband_for_pirate">
        Pirate contraband detected. Keep warships away.
    </string>
    <string name="ally_status_contraband_for_tsn">
        Pirate contraband detected. Send a warship to intercept.
    </string>
    <string name="ally_status_data_for_pirate">Secure data detected. Do not approach.</string>
    <string name="ally_status_data_for_tsn">
        Secure data detected. Do not permit enemy ships to intercept.
    </string>
    <string name="ally_status_deep_strike">Friendly ship, ready to assist in Deep Strike.</string>
    <string name="ally_status_fighter_trap">
        Fighter trap. Do not approach under any circumstances.
    </string>
    <string name="ally_status_hostage">
        Crew taken hostage. Captors demand 900 energy units in ransom.
    </string>
    <string name="ally_status_malfunction">
        Onboard computer is malfunctioning. Use EMP to reset it.
    </string>
    <string name="ally_status_mine_trap">
        Mine trap. Do not approach under any circumstances.
    </string>
    <string name="ally_status_needs_damcon">
        Damages detected. Requesting DamCon team member to conduct repairs.
    </string>
    <string name="ally_status_needs_energy">
        Out of energy. Requesting 100 units to start moving.
    </string>
    <string name="ally_status_normal">Friendly ship, ready to accept orders.</string>
    <string name="ally_status_repairing">Friendly ship, currently undergoing repairs.</string>
    <string name="ally_status_reward">
        Friendly ship, en route to a station to deliver a reward for your assistance.
    </string>
    <string name="alive">Alive</string>
    <string name="artemis_version_not_supported">Artemis %1$s not supported</string>
    <string name="attack_nearest_enemy">Attack</string>
    <string name="audio">Audio</string>
    <string name="auto_dismissal">Auto-dismissal</string>
    <string name="available_servers">Available servers</string>
    <string name="avoidance_black_hole">Black holes</string>
    <string name="avoidance_mine">Mines</string>
    <string name="avoidance_typhon">Typhons</string>
    <string name="avoidances">Avoidances</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
    <string name="biomech_rage">Status: %1$s</string>
    <string name="biomech_cannot_freeze">Freeze limit reached; cannot freeze again</string>
    <string name="biomech_frozen">Frozen - reanimation estimated in %1$d:%2$02d</string>
    <string name="biomech_moving">Mobile; touch to freeze</string>
    <string name="biomech_notification">Reanimation imminent.</string>
    <string name="biomech_will_move">Frozen - reanimation imminent</string>
    <string name="border_war_status">Border War: %1$s</string>
    <string name="build">Build</string>
    <string name="build_timer">ready in %1$d:%2$02d</string>
    <string name="building">Building:</string>
    <string name="cancel">Cancel</string>
    <string name="cannot_taunt">Cannot taunt</string>
    <string name="channel_allies_deep_string">Deep Strike production</string>
    <string name="channel_biomech_moving">Reanimation alert</string>
    <string name="channel_connection">Connection</string>
    <string name="channel_game_info">Game info</string>
    <string name="channel_game_over">Game over</string>
    <string name="channel_group_allies">Allies</string>
    <string name="channel_group_biomechs">Biomechs</string>
    <string name="channel_group_important">Important</string>
    <string name="channel_group_missions">Missions</string>
    <string name="channel_group_stations">Stations</string>
    <string name="channel_mission_completed">Mission completed</string>
    <string name="channel_mission_progress">Mission progress</string>
    <string name="channel_mission_new">New mission</string>
    <string name="channel_station_destroyed">Station destroyed</string>
    <string name="channel_station_production">Missile production</string>
    <string name="channel_station_attack">Station under attack</string>
    <string name="check_for_updates">Check for updates</string>
    <string name="click_scan">Press Scan to listen for broadcasting servers.</string>
    <string name="closest_station">Closest: %1$s</string>
    <string name="colon">:</string>
    <string name="command">Command</string>
    <string name="completed">Completed</string>
    <string name="connect">Connect</string>
    <string name="connected">Connected!</string>
    <string name="connecting">Connecting…</string>
    <string name="connection_closed">Connection closed</string>
    <string name="connection_lost">Connection lost, trying to reconnect…</string>
    <string name="connection_timeout">Connection timeout</string>
    <string name="currently_moving_to_attack">Currently moving to attack %1$s.</string>
    <string name="currently_moving_to_heading">Currently moving to heading %1$s.</string>
    <string name="currently_moving_toward">Currently moving toward %1$s.</string>
    <string name="default_setting">Default</string>
    <string name="destroyed">Destroyed</string>
    <string name="direction">DIR %1$s</string>
    <string name="disable_ineffective_taunts">Disable ineffective taunts</string>
    <string name="disconnect_io_error">
        An I/O error has occurred. You have been disconnected from the server.\n\nError: %1$s
    </string>
    <string name="disconnect_parse">
        An unexpected error has occurred. You have been disconnected from the server.\n\nError: %1$s
    </string>
    <string name="disconnect_remote">The server has been terminated.</string>
    <string name="disconnect_unknown_error">
        An unknown error has occurred while trying to send a packet to the server. There may be a
        bug in Artemis Agent. Please report the issue on GitHub.\n\nError: %1$s
    </string>
    <string name="disconnect_unsupported_version_old">
        Artemis Agent only supports Artemis version %1$s or higher. You have been disconnected from
        the server because its version of Artemis is too old (%2$s).
    </string>
    <string name="disconnect_unsupported_version_new">
        You have been disconnected from the server because it runs Artemis version %1$s, which is
        beyond what Artemis Agent currently supports. An update to Artemis Agent is recommended.
    </string>
    <string name="dismiss">Dismiss</string>
    <string name="displayed_rewards">Displayed rewards</string>
    <string name="docked">Docked</string>
    <string name="docking">Docking</string>
    <string name="enemy">Enemy</string>
    <string name="enemy_status_brave">Brave</string>
    <string name="enemy_status_cowardly">Cowardly</string>
    <string name="enemy_status_duplicitous">Duplicitous</string>
    <string name="enemy_status_easily_offended">Easily offended</string>
    <string name="enemy_status_no_intel">No intel; second scan required</string>
    <string name="enemy_status_normal">Normal</string>
    <string name="exit_message">You will be disconnected from the server. Confirm exit?</string>
    <string name="failed_to_connect">Failed to connect</string>
    <string name="fighters">Fighters</string>
    <string name="freeze_duration">Freeze duration</string>
    <string name="friendly">Friendly</string>
    <string name="front_shield">F %1$.0f/%2$.0f</string>
    <string name="game">Game</string>
    <string name="go_defend">Go defend:</string>
    <string name="hail">Hail</string>
    <string name="has_energy">Has energy.</string>
    <string name="has_ordnance">Has ordnance.</string>
    <string name="heartbeat_timeout">Heartbeat timeout</string>
    <string name="help">Help</string>
    <string-array name="help_contents_about">
        <item>
            Written by Jordan Longstaff\n
        </item>
        <item>
            Special thanks to Robert J. Walker for writing the IAN (Interface for Artemis
            Networking) library, without which this app could not exist. IAN is available on GitHub.
            \n
        </item>
        <item>
            \u00a9 Copyright 2024. All rights reserved.
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="help_contents_allies">
        <item>
            The Allies page shows the statuses of all of the ally ships in the currently running
            simulation. This includes their shield strengths, direction and range of their
            locations, side missions, and any other important information.\n
        </item>
        <item>
            \nLike stations, ally ships communicate their statuses to Artemis Agent through Comms
            messages. The app automatically sends a status requests to all ally ships when the
            simulation starts, or if the app connects to a simulation in progress. You can also
            manually request status by pressing the Hail button.
        </item>
        <item>
            \nYou can also send commands to an ally ship by pressing the Command button. Commands
            include turning to a specific direction, attacking the nearest targest, and moving to
            defend or rendezvous with another station or ally ship. You can also return to the list
            of ally ships by pressing the Cancel button. Sending a command will return you to the
            list automatically, unless the "Manually return from commands" setting is turned on.
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="help_contents_basics">
        <item>
            After you have selected your ship, you will be moved to the Game page. This page shows
            all of the in-game information relevant to the app. Most of it is split among multiple
            subpages, and you can choose which page is shown using the page selector located below
            the ship\'s name.\n
        </item>
        <item>
            \nAside from this information, there are three important controls on this page. The
            first is the Inventory button, which opens a dialog showing the ship\'s current ordnance
            stocks and single-seat craft inventory. The second is the Alert button, which toggles
            the ship\'s \"red alert\" status. The third is the Agent button.\n
        </item>
        <item>
            In order to use the Agent button, the player ship must acquire secret code cases, which
            can be used to force an enemy ship to surrender. You can activate one of those secret
            code cases by pressing the Agent button, and it will remain active for five minutes, or
            until it is used to make an enemy ship surrender. Only one secret code case may be
            active at a time.
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="help_contents_biomechs">
        <item>
            The Biomechs page shows the statuses of Biomech ships. Biomechs are generally neutral,
            but can occasionally turn aggressive and attack something nearby on a whim. If they are
            attacked, they will turn hostile and attack the player ship or ally ships more often.\n
        </item>
        <item>
            \nYou can stop a Biomech from moving or attacking anything by freezing it. To freeze a
            Biomech, simply tap it in the list in the page. The effects of freezing a Biomech will
            last for only a few minutes; the exact amount of time is determined by the server, but
            seems to vary slightly and is not communicated to the app, so therefore the app has to
            estimate it. You can specify the estimated duration in the Settings page. Biomechs can
            only be frozen a maximum of three times.
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="help_contents_enemies">
        <item>
            The Enemies page is for communications with enemy ships.\n
        </item>
        <item>
            \nEnemies are hostile and must be defeated as swiftly as possible. Destroying them will
            suffice, but convincing them to surrender may be preferred. Enemies are identified when
            they are scanned by the Science officer; however, a second scan is required to obtain
            intel. Press the Show button to access any intel obtained, as well as the selection of
            taunts.\n
        </item>
        <item>
            \nIf an enemy has been sufficiently damaged, they may surrender. To do that, you must
            send a message asking for a surrender by pressing the Surrender button. Surrender
            messages are only effective within a certain range; you can configure the app to disable
            the Surrender button against an enemy that is too far away in the Settings page.
        </item>
        <item>
            \nTaunts are used to provoke an enemy to attack the player ship, thus luring it away
            from another target (e.g. a friendly station). Unlike surrenders, taunts are not
            restricted by distance. However, not all taunts will work; intel obtained by Science
            includes which of the taunts, dependent on the enemy\'s race, will not work. If that
            taunt is used, the enemy will ignore it and all subsequent attempts to taunt. The other
            taunts will work, but generally only once each.
        </item>
        <item>
            \nThe Settings page has several options to organize the list of enemies. In certain
            combinations, they can be organized by race, name, distance, and whether or not they\'ve
            surrendered. You can use the category buttons at the top to quickly scroll through the
            list. The info displayed in the list for an enemy includes its direction, range, number
            of successful taunts, and a brief summary of intel about the captain of the enemy ship,
            which may be one of the following, assuming intel has been obtained (note that this does
            not include information relevant to taunts):\n
        </item>
        <item>
            \u2022 Normal: No outstanding characteristics.\n
        </item>
        <item>
            \u2022 Brave: Less likely to surrender.\n
        </item>
        <item>
            \u2022 Cowardly: More likely to surrender.\n
        </item>
        <item>
            \u2022 Duplicitous: Surrenders are not permanent.\n
        </item>
        <item>
            \u2022 Easily offended: Taunts will work more than once, possibly including ones that
            normally wouldn\'t work at all.
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="help_contents_getting_started">
        <item>
            Welcome to Artemis Agent! If this is your first time using this app, this tutorial will
            teach you all you need to know about how to use it.\n
        </item>
        <item>
            Artemis Agent is a Comms client app designed to be used with Artemis Spaceship Bridge
            Simulator, developed by Thom Robertson. It will be your assistant in managing side
            missions, ally ships, stations and more.\n
        </item>
        <item>
            Before you can use Artemis Agent, you must have an Artemis server running. Open Artemis
            on your computer and click \"Start Server\". After that, enter the server\'s address
            into the Address bar at the top of the screen, then touch the Connect button on the
            right to connect to the server. If the server version is 2.7.0 or greater, you can scan
            for the presence of the server by pressing the Scan button.\n
        </item>
        <item>
            \nAfter the app has connected to the server, you must select a ship. The Ships page
            shows the list of ships to choose from with complete descriptions. Once you select a
            ship, the app will join that ship as a Comms client.\n
        </item>
        <item>
            \nIf you press the Home button on your device, Artemis Agent will continue to run in the
            background. It will continue to receive information via a Comms service and display it
            in notifications on your device. In general, you can return to Artemis Agent by tapping
            any of the notifications.\n
        </item>
        <item>
            If the Artemis server has a mod, you will need to provide a vessel data XML file that
            matches that of the server. By default, Artemis Agent provides a vessel data file for
            the stock version of Artemis. If you need to use a different set of vessel data, you
            can specify the file\'s location in the Settings page. The location that you set will
            point to either the app\'s internal assets, your device\'s internal storage, or, if
            applicable, an SD card. Keep in mind that changing this value while the app is connected
            to a server will automatically terminate the connection.
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="help_contents_missions">
        <item>
            The Missions page shows all currently active side missions. Side missions occur during a
            running simulation and offer the player an opportunity to acquire various bonuses that
            last for the remainder of the simulation. These side missions are issued to the Comms
            officer by an ally ship or station, and include instructions to visit another ship or
            station before going there to receive a reward. For example, Comms may receive a message
            like this:\n
        </item>
        <item>
            \nThis message gives you the following information:\n
        </item>
        <item>
            1. First, you are being told to go to Y27 (a friendly ship) and rendezvous with it. To
            rendezvous with a friendly ship means to pass within 500 metres of it.\n
        </item>
        <item>
            2. Second, after that, you must go to DS3, the sender of the message, and dock there.\n
        </item>
        <item>
            3. Finally, your reward is that DS3 will double its production speed.\n
        </item>
        <item>
            The Missions page shows all such missions received in a list, also listing the two
            destination points in the order that they must be visited, as well as the direction and
            range to the next one. Although each side mission only offers one reward, the list will
            be compressed as much as possible by merging entries with the same waypoints. In this
            way, a single entry in the list may show multiple rewards. If a reward would be received
            more than once, a \"x2\" or similar multiplier will by shown for that reward. Be sure to
            pay attention to all rewards shown within a single entry.\n
        </item>
        <item>
            \nThe rewards you receive for completing side missions are as
            follows:\n
        </item>
        <item>
            \u2022 Battery Charge: Your ship will receive some additional energy.\n
        </item>
        <item>
            \u2022 Extra Coolant: Engineering will receive two additional units of coolant.\n
        </item>
        <item>
            \u2022 Nuke Torpedoes: Your ship will receive two additional Nuke torpedoes.\n
        </item>
        <item>
            \u2022 Production Speed: The station that issued the side mission will speed up its
            production of ordnances.\n
        </item>
        <item>
            \u2022 Shield Boost: The front and rear shield capacities of your ship will increase.
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="help_contents_routing">
        <item>
            The Routing page shows routing information. Artemis Agent calculates optimized routes to
            various destinations in the background. When helping ally ships, completing side
            missions or going to restock ordnances at a station, it is useful to know the order in
            which to visit them that maximizes rewards while minimizing travel time.\n
        </item>
        <item>
            \nMultiple types of objectives can be chosen, determining what destinations are shown,
            what order they are shown in, what the order means, and what information is shown for
            each that is relevant to the chosen objective. If the Tasks objective is selected, the
            route shown will be the optimal order of destinations to visit to complete all of the
            listed objectives, which include both side missions and ally ships in need of help.\n
        </item>
        <item>
            \nIf the Supplies objective is selected, the route shown will not be a singular route,
            but rather a list of all stations organized in order of convenience. Convenience in this
            case means both availability of the desired supplies and the optimal distance calculated
            to reach the station. You can also select which supplies you want; they can be any type
            of ordnance or replacement fighters. Your current stock and capacity of each supply is
            listed when you go to select them. It is recommended that you only choose supplies where
            your current stock is less than the maximum capacity, as these are supplies that you
            actually need.\n
        </item>
        <item>
            Regardless of objective, optimized routes are calculated with certain dangerous objects
            taken into account. These dangerous objects include black holes, mines and Typhon space
            monsters. You can disable or adjust these avoidances in Settings. Note that having
            avoidances taken into consideration means more work for the routing algorithm. Also note
            that avoidances are not considered for player ships with jump drives. Finally, keep in
            mind that due to the complex nature of the routing process, an heuristic algorithm is
            used for efficiency, and therefore the route shown will not necessarily be optimal; it
            is expected that the Science officer uses the displayed order and cross-references it
            against their map to determine the optimal route.
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="help_contents_stations">
        <item>
            The Stations page shows information about all of the docking stations in the currently
            running simulation. This includes shield strengths, direction and range of their
            locations, production speeds, side missions, stores of replacement fighters, and current
            ordnance stocks.\n
        </item>
        <item>
            \nOnly one friendly station at a time is shown, but you can use the selector at the top
            to choose which one is currently being displayed. You can also press the Closest Station
            button at the bottom to switch to the station that is closest to the ship\'s current
            location.\n
        </item>
        <item>
            Ordnance and replacement fighter stock information is received from the server via Comms
            messages. Artemis Agent frequently sends messages to each station requesting status
            updates; the following are examples of circumstances where requests are sent:\n
        </item>
        <item>
            \u2022 when the simulation starts;\n
        </item>
        <item>
            \u2022 when the app connects to a simulation in progress;\n
        </item>
        <item>
            \u2022 when the station finishes building ordnance;\n
        </item>
        <item>
            \u2022 when the station receives a request to build ordnance of a specific type; or\n
        </item>
        <item>
            \u2022 when the user manually requests a status update by pressing the Status button.\n
        </item>
        <item>
            Pressing the Standby button will send a request to the station to stand by for docking.
            This is recommended when the player ship intends to dock at the station, which is
            typically done to refuel, recharge shields and restock ordnances, because having a
            station prepare itself ahead of time makes these recovery operations more efficient.\n
        </item>
        <item>
            As stations continually build more ordnances, that information is also displayed. At the
            bottom of the page, you can both see and choose what type of ordnance the station is
            currently building, along with the amount of time before the station is expected to
            finish building it. This amount of time is calculated based on the type of ordnance and
            the station\'s production speed, which varies based on the type of station and increases
            whenever a Production Speed side mission is completed.\n
        </item>
        <item>
            In a Deep Strike or Border War simulation, the Stations page is also able to show enemy
            stations. These stations simply appear in a list and only show shield strength and
            location information. There is also a separate list that shows all the names of stations
            that have been destroyed.
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="help_topics_about">About</string>
    <string name="help_topics_allies">Allies</string>
    <string name="help_topics_basics">Basics</string>
    <string name="help_topics_biomechs">Biomechs</string>
    <string name="help_topics_enemies">Enemies</string>
    <string name="help_topics_getting_started">Getting started</string>
    <string name="help_topics_missions">Missions</string>
    <string name="help_topics_routing">Routing</string>
    <string name="help_topics_stations">Stations</string>
    <string name="included_incentives">Included incentives</string>
    <string name="infinity">\u221E</string>
    <string name="inventory">Inv</string>
    <string name="io_parse_error">I/O parse error</string>
    <string name="io_write_error">I/O write error</string>
    <string name="kilometres">km</string>
    <string name="left">Left</string>
    <string name="manually_return_from_commands">Manually return from commands</string>
    <string name="manufacturing_torpedoes">Torpedoes will be ready in %1$d:%2$02d.</string>
    <string name="manufacturing_torpedoes_ready">Torpedoes ready.</string>
    <string name="milliseconds">ms</string>
    <string name="mission_battery">Battery</string>
    <string name="mission_completed">Mission completed</string>
    <string name="mission_coolant">Coolant</string>
    <string name="mission_nuke">Nuke</string>
    <string name="mission_production">Production</string>
    <string name="mission_shield">Shield</string>
    <string name="mission_will_be_removed">Will be removed in %1$ds</string>
    <string name="more_commands">More commands:</string>
    <string name="next_to">Next: %1$s %2$s %3$s</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="no_enemies">Scanned enemies will be displayed here.</string>
    <string name="no_servers_found">Could not find any local servers.</string>
    <string name="no_ships">Connect to a server.</string>
    <string name="no_ship_selected">Select a ship.</string>
    <string name="no_stations">No stations.</string>
    <string name="none">None</string>
    <string name="not_connected">Not connected</string>
    <string name="off">Off</string>
    <string name="on">On</string>
    <string name="ordnance_stock">%1$s: %2$d/%3$d</string>
    <string name="play">Play</string>
    <string name="proceed_to_your_destination">Proceed</string>
    <string name="range">RANGE %1$.0f</string>
    <string name="rear_shield">R %1$.0f/%2$.0f</string>
    <string name="reason_ambassador">pick up ambassador</string>
    <string name="reason_commandeered">liberate commandeered ship</string>
    <string name="reason_has_energy">receive energy</string>
    <string name="reason_hostage">rescue hostages</string>
    <string name="reason_malfunction">reset broken computer</string>
    <string name="reason_needs_damcon">transfer DamCon personnel</string>
    <string name="reason_needs_energy">deliver energy</string>
    <string name="reason_pirate_boss">pick up boss</string>
    <string name="recent_address_limit">Recent address limit</string>
    <string name="refreeze">Re-freeze</string>
    <string name="rendezvous_with">Rendezvous with:</string>
    <string name="restore_default_settings">Restore defaults</string>
    <string name="reverse_sorting_by_race">Reverse sorting by race</string>
    <string name="review_error">Review Error</string>
    <string name="review_error_message">
        Review flow failed to start. Please try again later.\n\nError: %1$s
    </string>
    <string name="review_prompt">
        You are advised to rate this app in the Google Play Store. Proceed?
    </string>
    <string name="review_title">
        Enjoying Artemis Agent?
    </string>
    <string name="rewards">Rewards: %1$s</string>
    <string-array name="reward_type_entries">
        <item>Battery Charge</item>
        <item>Extra Coolant</item>
        <item>Nuke Torpedoes</item>
        <item>Production Speed</item>
        <item>Shield Boost</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="right">Right</string>
    <string name="route_for_supplies">Route for supplies</string>
    <string name="route_incentive_missions">Missions</string>
    <string name="route_incentive_needs_damcon">Needs DamCon</string>
    <string name="route_incentive_needs_energy">Needs energy</string>
    <string name="route_incentive_has_energy">Has energy</string>
    <string name="route_incentive_malfunction">Malfunction</string>
    <string name="route_incentive_ambassador">Ambassador</string>
    <string name="route_incentive_hostage">Hostage</string>
    <string name="route_incentive_commandeered">Commandeered</string>
    <string name="scan">Scan</string>
    <string name="scan_timeout">Scan timeout</string>
    <string name="seconds">sec</string>
    <string name="selected">Selected</string>
    <string name="send">Send</string>
    <string name="server_port">Server port</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="settings_menu_client">Client settings</string>
    <string name="settings_menu_connection">Connection settings</string>
    <string name="settings_menu_missions">Mission settings</string>
    <string name="settings_menu_allies">Ally settings</string>
    <string name="settings_menu_enemies">Enemy settings</string>
    <string name="settings_menu_biomechs">Biomech settings</string>
    <string name="settings_menu_routing">Routing settings</string>
    <string name="settings_menu_personal">Personal settings</string>
    <string name="setup">Setup</string>
    <string name="ship_number">Ship %1$d</string>
    <string name="ships">Ships</string>
    <string name="show_destroyed_allies">Show destroyed allies</string>
    <string name="show_intel">Show intel</string>
    <string name="show_taunt_status">Show taunt status</string>
    <string name="single_seat_craft_docked">%1$d single-seat craft docked</string>
    <string name="single_seat_craft_launched">%1$d single-seat craft launched</string>
    <string name="single_seat_craft_lost">%1$d single-seat craft lost</string>
    <string name="sort_by_class">Class</string>
    <string name="sort_by_energy">En</string>
    <string name="sort_by_name">Name</string>
    <string name="sort_by_race">Race</string>
    <string name="sort_by_range">Range</string>
    <string name="sort_by_status">Status</string>
    <string name="sort_methods">Sort methods</string>
    <string name="sound_volume">Sound volume</string>
    <string name="standby">Standby</string>
    <string name="station_shield">SHLD %1$.0f/%2$.0f</string>
    <string name="station_speed">Speed factor %1$.1f</string>
    <string name="status">Status</string>
    <string name="stock_of_ordnance">%1$d of %2$s</string>
    <string name="supplies">Supplies</string>
    <string name="surrender">Surrender</string>
    <string name="surrender_range">Surrender range</string>
    <string name="surrendered">Surrendered</string>
    <string name="surrendered_duplicitous">Surrendered; duplicitous</string>
    <string name="tap_to_dismiss">Tap to dismiss</string>
    <string name="tasks">Tasks</string>
    <string name="taunt">Taunt</string>
    <string name="taunts_many">Taunted %d times</string>
    <string name="taunts_one">Taunted once</string>
    <string name="taunts_two">Taunted twice</string>
    <string name="taunts_zero">Has not been taunted</string>
    <string name="theme">Theme</string>
    <string name="then_to">Then: %1$s %2$s %3$s</string>
    <string name="three_digit_directions">Three-digit directions</string>
    <string name="turn_to_heading">Turn to:</string>
    <string name="unknown">Unknown</string>
    <string name="unknown_error">Unknown error</string>
    <string name="update_interval">Update interval</string>
    <string name="vessel_data">Vessel data</string>
    <string name="vessel_data_external">External</string>
    <string name="vessel_data_internal">Internal</string>
    <string name="vessel_data_xml_location">Vessel data XML location</string>
    <string name="waiting_for_game">Waiting for game to start…</string>
    <string name="xml_error">XML Error</string>
    <string name="xml_error_message">
        Vessel data could not be loaded. There is an error in the XML file. The setting has been
        reverted. Either resolve the error or delete the XML file.\n\nError: %1$s
    </string>
    <string name="xml_location_warning">
        WARNING: There is an active connection to an Artemis server. The connection will be
        terminated if you change the vessel data. Proceed?
    </string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
</resources>
